namemesh.com 2018-10-30

# Privacy Policy - NameMesh

Last Updated: 28 May 2013

We respect and protect the privacy of our users and take appropriate steps to safeguard your personal information. This Privacy Policy outlines NameMesh’ commitment to practices regarding the collection, sharing and use of information from users of the NameMesh.com website (the “Website”). If we make changes to this policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on the Website and change the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. Persons under the age of 13 are not permitted to use the Website.

## Information Collection and Usage

Like most website operators, NameMesh collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. NameMesh’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how NameMesh’s visitors use its website. NameMesh also collects personal information from you, such as name and email address, when you sign up for our service or contact us by email. We also track the actions you take on our site in order to improve the service. We will never share this information with anyone for any reason unless required by law. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. NameMesh uses cookies to help NameMesh identify and track visitors, their usage of NameMesh website, and their website access preferences. NameMesh visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using NameMesh’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of NameMesh’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. We use cookies to uniquely identify your session for a more efficient user experience while visiting our Website.

## Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by NameMesh and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Information Sharing

NameMesh does not disclose, sell or rent your personally identifiable information or search data to any third parties except for statistical purposes as outline above. NameMesh discloses personally identifiable information and potentially personally identifiable information (such as your IP address) only to those of its employees, service providers and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf or to provide, operate or provide services for the Website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. We may disclose personally identifiable information to cooperate with law enforcement authorities, a court or administrative agency, or other governmental authority in connection with an investigation or where required by applicable law. We may also disclose any activities or information about you to law enforcement, other government officials or other third parties (such as intellectual property owners) as we, in our sole discretion, determine necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or any other activity that is illegal or may expose NameMesh, its users or other third parties to harm. If NameMesh, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that NameMesh goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of NameMesh may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

## Information Security

The security of your personally identifiable information is important to us. We use reasonable security measures to help protect this information, including without limitation, limiting access to your personal information to those of our employees and service providers who require it to operate the Website and provide services to you. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us via e-mail at contact@namemesh.com.

## Links to Third Party Sites

This Policy only applies to the NameMesh website and services. We do not exercise control over the sites that our service links to. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, and collect data or solicit personal information from you. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and NameMesh and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party. We encourage you to read privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. 

## Privacy Policy Changes

NameMesh may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in NameMesh’s sole discretion. NameMesh encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Visitors can always check the “Last Updated” date at the top of this document to see when the Privacy Policy was last changed. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
